<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Visit Ouro Preto</string>
    <string name="ouro_preto">Ouro Preto</string>

    <!-- Image and Photo credits and subtitles -->
    <string name="main_photo">Church São Francisco de Paula (Photo by Ana Paula)</string>
    <string name="city_and_mountains">City and mountains (Photo by Ana Paula)</string>
    <string name="vila_rica">Villa Rica de Ouro Preto (19th century)</string>
    <string name="flag">Official flag of Ouro Preto</string>
    <string name="seal">Official seal of Ouro Preto</string>
    <string name="food_photo">Mineira Food</string>
    <string name="church_and_mountains">Church São Francisco de Paula (Photo by Ana Paula)</string>
    <string name="map">Ouro Preto MG Map</string>


    <!-- Drawer items -->
    <string name="nav_header_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Discover more about Ouro Preto</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="photos">Photos</string>
    <string name="videos">Videos</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>

    <!-- Menu items -->
    <string name="category_main">Home</string>
    <string name="category_see">To see</string>
    <string name="category_do">To do</string>
    <string name="category_eat">To eat</string>


    <!-- Long texts -->
    <string name="intro_title">Welcome to Visit Ouro Preto Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Ouro Preto (Black Gold) is a city in the state of Minas Gerais,
        Brazil. Located in one of the main areas of the Brazilian Gold Rush in Espinhaço mountains,
        it was a former colonial mining town and now it\'s considered a World Heritage Site by
        UNESCO because of its outstanding Baroque architecture.\n\nOuro Preto is one of Brazil\'s
        best-preserved colonial towns and it is one of the most popular travelling destinations in
        the country.\n\nIf you want to know more about the History, Climate, Art and Culinary of Ouro Preto and
        Minas Gerais state, just keep scrolling down. To see tourist attractions, scroll left or
        navigate using the menu above.</string>

    <string name="history_title">History &amp; Art</string>
    <string name="history_text">
        Founded at the end of the 17th century, Ouro Preto was originally called Vila Rica (meaning
        Rich Village), the focal point of the gold rush and Brazil\'s golden age in the 18th century
        under Portuguese rule.\n\nOfficially, 800 tons of gold were sent from Ouro Preto to Portugal in the 18th century.
        Other gold circulated illegally, and still other gold remained in the colony to adorn
        churches and for other uses. In the 18th century, Vila Rica was the largest city in Brazil
        and one of the most populous cities in the New World, with 100,000 inhabitants, but its
        importance declined after the state capital was moved to Belo Horizonte in 1889.\n\n
        The city centre contains well-preserved Portuguese colonial architecture, with few signs of
        modern urban development. New construction must keep with the city\'s historical aesthetic.
        \n\nThe tremendous wealth from gold mining in the 18th century created a city which attracted
        the intelligentsia of Europe. Philosophy and art flourished, and evidence of a baroque
        revival called the "Barroco Mineiro" is illustrated in architecture as well as by sculptors
        such as Aleijadinho, painters such as Mestre Athayde, composers such as Lobo de Mesquita,
        and poets such as Tomás António Gonzaga.\n\n18th and 19th century churches decorated with gold and the sculptured works of Aleijadinho
        make Ouro Preto a tourist destination.
        </string>

    <string name="culinary_title">Culinary</string>
    <string name="culinary_text">Food in Minas Gerais is an attraction simply by itself, and this local
        Brazilian cuisine alone justifies a trip to Ouro Preto. The typical dishes of Ouro Preto
        have distinct personalities and accents, originating in the union of different people and
        ethnic groups that give the region a sense of diversity. An equally diverse number of
        Ouro Preto restaurants will give you the chance to try Minas Gerais cuisine firsthand.
    </string>

    <string name="climate_title">Climate &amp; Location</string>
    <string name="climate_text">Located at 1,179 m (3,868 ft) above sea level, Ouro Preto has a
        subtropical highland climate (Cwb, according to the Köppen climate classification), with
        warm and humid summers and mild, dry winters. Frost is occasional and occur in June and
        July. There is a report of snow in the city in the year of 1843.</string>


    <string name="more_info">More information:</string>

    <!-- To See -->
    <string name="to_see_title_one">Church of Saint Francis of Assisi</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_one">This unique rococo-style church, built in 1776, is arguably
        Aleijadinho\'s greatest work. The circular bell towers and the oculus closed by a relief
        were original features in religious architecture of that time in Brazil. The facade has a
        single entrance door under a soapstone frontispiece under a relief depicting Saint Francis
        receiving the stigmata. The interior is richly decorated with golden woodwork, statues and
        paintings, and the wooden ceiling displays a painting by Manuel da Costa Ataíde.</string>
    <string name="to_see_address_one">Location: Ouro Preto &#8211; State of Minas Gerais, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_one">Hours: 8:30AM–5PM except Mondays</string>

    <string name="to_see_title_two">Itacolomi State Park</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_two"> Shared by the municipalities of Ouro Preto and Mariana is a park
        which contains very diverse flora and fauna with many hiking opportunities. The centerpiece
        of the park, Itacolomi Peak, is a pair of rocks, one huge and one much smaller, which can be
        seen from hilltops around town. Itacolomi means "the Rock and the Boy" in Tupi-Guarani. For
        experienced hikers, it is possible to take a difficult 12 km trek through the park to visit
        the village of Lavras Novas and its nearby waterfalls. Visitors to the park must be
        accompanied by a guide, which can be arranged in advance by telephone.</string>
    <string name="to_see_address_two">Location: Rodovia BR 356 Km 98, s/n, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_two">Hours: 8AM–5PM except Mondays</string>

    <string name="to_see_title_three">Conspiracy Museum (Museu da Inconfidência)</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_three">This museum is dedicated to the memory of the Inconfidência
        Mineira, an unsuccessful 1789 revolt against Portuguese rule which was inspired by the
        American Revolution. The building, itself one of the best extant specimens of colonial
        baroque architecture, houses the remains of some the revolutionaries, a library and
        archives, as well as works by artists of the period, including works by Aleijadinho and
        Manuel da Costa Ataíde. </string>
    <string name="to_see_address_three">Location: Praça Tiradentes, 139 &#8211; Centro Histórico, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_three">Hours: 10AM–6PM except Mondays</string>

    <string name="to_see_title_four">Church of Nossa Senhora do Pilar</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_four">The oldest church in the city was designed by one of
        Aleijadinho\'s mentors and completed in 1731 to replace the original main church.
        Despite the rather stark outward appearance, the interior glistens with almost 1000 pounds
        of gold and almost 900 pounds of silver. The basement of the church holds the Museum of
        Sacred Art. </string>
    <string name="to_see_address_four">Location: Praça Monsenhor Castilho Barbosa, 17 &#8211; Pilar, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_four">Hours: 8:30AM–5PM except Mondays</string>

    <string name="to_see_title_five">Mina da Passagem (Mine of the Crossing)</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_five"> Located in the city of Mariana MG (5 miles from Ouro Preto),
        this is the world\'s largest mine open to the public. In order to reach the mining galleries
        a small trolley is used and it is held by a steel cable.
        You descend for 315 meters and the total depth reaches 120 meters. The visit to the mine is
        accompanied by a guide (who normally does not speak English, so make sure you have someone
        who can translate for you). Apart from the grandiosity of the excavation, there is also a
        beautiful underground lake. </string>
    <string name="to_see_address_five">Location: 192 Rua Eugênio Eduardo Raballo, Mariana &#8211; MG, 35420&#8211;000, Brazil </string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_five">Hours: 9AM–5PM</string>

    <string name="to_see_title_six">Casa dos Contos Museum (Tax Collection House Museum)</string>
    <string name="to_see_text_six"> Built between 1782 and 1784, Casa dos Contos was home to João
        Rodrigues de Macedo, the administrator of tax collection and one of the wealthiest men in
        18th century colonial Brazil. Tax money owed to the Portuguese crown was paid at the house.
        Macedo was also one of the most eminent supporters of the underground Independence Movement
        of Minas Gerais state (the Inconfidência) in 1789. Ironically, this colonial baroque
        structure served as a jail for revolutionaries in the late 18th century.  </string>
    <string name="to_see_address_six">Location: R. São José, 12 &#8211; Centro Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil </string>
    <string name="to_see_hours_six">Hours: 10AM–5PM</string>

    <!-- To Do -->
    <string name="to_do_title_one">Holy Week processions</string>
    <string name="to_do_text_one">Easter week brings lavish celebration to the streets around the
        four parishes of the town. In the late night and morning hours after Saturday night’s Easter
        Vigil, townspeople decorate the cobblestone streets with a tapete, or carpet, of colored
        wood shavings to mark the hilly, one kilometer route for the next morning\'s Easter
        procession. Everybody can participate in the making of the carpets. Ouro Preto culminates
        its Holy Week observances with a 6 a.m. Mass at St. Francis of Assisi and a procession along
        the 1 km route covered that decorated the night before.</string>
    <string name="to_do_address_one">Location: Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_do_hours_one">Date: Between March and April </string>

    <string name="to_do_title_two">Winter Festival</string>
    <string name="to_do_text_two"> In July, the Winter Festival is held in Ouro Preto, and it
        invades the streets, hills, parks, theaters and cinema. One of the country\'s largest
        cultural events, the Winter Festival brings together performing arts, music, visual arts and
        literature, with workshops and cultural events. The event is organized by the Universidade
        Federal de Ouro Preto (Federal University of Ouro Preto).</string>
    <string name="to_do_address_two">Location: Ouro Preto, Mariana and João Monlevade</string>
    <string name="to_do_hours_two">Date: 07/06/2018 &#8211; 07/22/2018 </string>

    <string name="to_do_title_three">Carnaval</string>
    <string name="to_do_text_three">The street carnaval in Ouro Preto attracts thousands of people
        every year. Traditional band music is played across town, and many people dress up in
        costumes during the holiday. There are two main types of street parade in town: the one with
        samba schools and the one with blocos (blocks). Carnaval usually takes place in February or
        March, depending on the timing of Lent. It starts on the Saturday immediately before Lent
        and ends the day before Ash Wednesday. Ouro Preto has the oldest carnival block in Brazil:
        Zé Pereira dos Lacaios, founded in 1867.</string>
    <string name="to_do_address_three">Location: Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, Brazil </string>
    <string name="to_do_hours_three">Date: 02/09/2018 &#8211; 02/14/2018 </string>

    <string name="to_do_title_four">Soapstone Handicraft Fair</string>
    <string name="to_do_text_four">Popularly known as Soapstone Fair, the Association of Exhibitors
        of Largo do Coimbra have been meeting, since 1995 in front of the Church of Saint Francis of
        Assisi, to commercialize and exhibit their works. Historical sources indicate that the space
        where the fair is located has been a point for exchanges and sales of goods and services
        since 1824. Today, the fair has more than 50 tents and attracts tourists from all over the
        world. There you can buy jewelry, such as necklaces, earrings, rings and bracelets,
        embroidered t-shirts and caps, precious stones and decorative pieces of soapstone.
        This is a great place to buy gifts and keep memories of Ouro Preto.</string>
    <string name="to_do_address_four">Location: Largo do Coimbra, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_do_hours_four">Hours: 7AM–7PM</string>

    <!-- to Eat - all texts taken from https://www.lonelyplanet.com -->
    <string name="to_eat_title_one">Casa do Ouvidor</string>
    <string name="to_eat_text_one">Just downhill from Praça Tiradentes, Ouvidor has garnered
        numerous awards for its comida mineira. At night, low lighting enhances the rustic charm of
        the ancient upstairs dining room. Definitely come with an empty stomach – portions are
        immense.</string>
    <string name="to_eat_address_one">Location: 42 &#8211; Centro Rua Direita, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_eat_hours_one">Hours: 11AM–3PM, 7–10PM</string>

    <string name="to_eat_title_two">Café Geraes &amp; Escadabaixo</string>
    <string name="to_eat_text_two"> Well-heeled students and artists favor this trendy spot to sip
        wine, talk shop and linger over creatively prepared salads, pasta, salmon and steak dishes.
        On weekdays, there\'s a good-value prato executivo lunch – main dish, salad, dessert and
        coffee for $8. Their downstairs space Escadabaixo serves the exact same menu, but with
        more of a cellar beer-hall atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="to_eat_address_two">Location: Rua Direita, 122 &#8211; centro, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_eat_hours_two">Hours: 12PM–12AM (Closed Tuesdays) </string>

    <string name="to_eat_title_three">Bené da Flauta</string>
    <string name="to_eat_text_three">Occupying two levels of a gorgeous colonial sobrado (mansion)
        just below Igreja de São Francisco, this upscale restaurant is ideal for a romantic dinner,
        with pretty views of Ouro Preto\'s hillsides, candlelight reflecting off tall multi-paned
        windows, and Brazilian jazz on the sound system. The menu of trout, steak, pasta and mineira
        specialties is complemented by a good wine list. </string>
    <string name="to_eat_address_three">Location: R. São Francisco de Assis, 32 &#8211; Centro, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_eat_hours_three">Hours: 12–11:30PM</string>

    <string name="to_eat_title_four">Chafariz</string>
    <string name="to_eat_text_four">Eclectically decorated with old photos, religious art, Brazilian
        flags and antiques, this local institution serves one of Minas\' tastiest (if priciest)
        buffets. The menu showcases traditional local favorites such as lombo (roasted pork loin)
        and feijão tropeiro, followed by Minas cheese and goiabada (guava paste) for dessert.
        Post-meal shots of cachaça, coffee and jabuticaba liqueur are included in the price. </string>
    <string name="to_eat_address_four">Location: 167, R. São José &#8211; Centro, Ouro Preto &#8211; MG, 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_eat_hours_four">Hours: 11:30AM-4PM (Closed Monday)</string>

    <string name="to_eat_title_five">O Passo</string>
    <string name="to_eat_text_five"> In a lovely 18th-century building with intimate candlelit
        interior, this local favorite specializes in pizza, pasta and salads complemented by a good
        wine list. Outside, the relaxed creekside terrace is ideal for an after-dinner drink. On
        Tuesday nights, don’t miss the rodizio de pizzas (all-you-can-eat pizza, $15). There's
        live jazz on Thursdays and Friday evenings, and during Sunday lunch. </string>
    <string name="to_eat_address_five">Location: Rua Sao Jose Downtown, Ouro Preto, State of Minas Gerais 35400&#8211;000, Brazil</string>
    <string name="to_eat_hours_five">Hours: 12PM–1AM </string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
